We've already gone over how a cup should fit, how a band should fit and the purpose of your strap.
But what we haven't gone over is that every company makes their bras differently.
For example, this company is called Natori, and they make a bra that is wider in the wire and shallow in the cup.
So while this bra is a 32 D, it's not for a D-cup who is fuller this way; it's for somebody who's more spread out this way.
And also, this company makes a very stretchy band, so if you find out that well you've been wearing a 34 inch band for years and years and years then you should be wearing a 32.
This is a great bra to start transitioning with because it stretches out a little bit quicker than others do.
Another example is this company called Freya.
Freya is a UK company, and they specialize in bras for women with bigger cup sizes, and smaller band sizes.
So, for example, if you know somebody who measures 26 inches around and is really busty on top, they might wear a 28 G. And they could get that from Freya.
UK sizing is a little different, so when you're in the store and you see numbers, ask for help.
A 28 E is an American DD.
So in America an E is the same as a UK F. And it just keeps going that way, so it's always good to ask for help because otherwise you'll just make yourself crazy.